# ADITI PARIKH

 $+447897606428 \Leftrightarrow London, UK$ 

aditi.parikh0526@gmail.com  $\diamond$  linkedin.com/in/aditi-parikh05  $\diamond$  www.aditiparikh.uk

### **OBJECTIVE**

Versatile Full Stack Developer with 2+ years of experience building web applications and AZ-900 certification in Microsoft Azure. Combining technical proficiency in front-end (React, Next and JavaScript) and back-end (Node.js, MongoDB, SQL) with strong problem-solving and communication skills, I seek to deliver scalable, cloud-integrated solutions in Azure or Full-Stack development roles.

#### **SKILLS**

Front-End HTML, CSS, Tailwind, ReactJS, Javascript, Typescript

Back-end NodeJS, ExpressJS, Socket.IO, Python

Frameworks NextJS, Flask, Bubble.IO

DevOps/Cloud Microsoft Azure (VM, Functions, WebApps), AWS (Lambda, API Gateway), Docker

Database SQL, Prisma, MongoDB

### **CERTIFICATIONS**

Microsoft Azure Fundamentals AZ-900

August 2024

Score: 857

The Complete 2022 Web Development Bootcamp

April 2021 - March 2022

Udemy: Dr. Angela Yu

### **EXPERIENCE**

## Full-Stack Engineer

Anima People

Nov 2024 - Present London, UK

- Spearheading the design and development of PsycSec's MVP, leveraging the combined strengths of Next.js, Node.js, Prisma, PostgreSQL, and Tailwind CSS to build a scalable, maintainable, and efficient application. Currently driving iterative improvements and feature enhancements, ensuring alignment with core product requirements and facilitating rapid feedback incorporation from stakeholders and users.
- Developed a role-based access control (RBAC) user dashboard utilising MFA, reducing unauthorised access incidents by 30% and enabling tailored access for key user roles. This improved operational efficiency, saving approximately 15% of support time previously spent on access and authentication issues.
- Connected and integrated APIs between front-end and back-end services and collaborating with the Data Science team to successfully deploy machine learning models by using AWS Gateway and Lambda. This real-time integration streamlined predictive analytics, reducing data processing time by 25% and supporting improved decision-making within the platform.
- Liaised with key stakeholders and investors during product demonstrations, effectively gathering feedback and aligning product functionality with business objectives, resulting in actionable improvements for further development.
- Managed version control through Git and coordinated with QA teams to maintain code integrity and stability, reducing deployment errors by 35% and ensuring faster bug resolution cycles, resulting in smoother production releases and increased development velocity.

Nov 2023 - Nov 2024 *London, UK* 

Kings College Hospital NHS Trust

- Organized and managed a comprehensive filing system that improved the efficiency of daily operations by 50%.
- Devised an automated file for registering life-cycle of reports from generation to postage into laboratories across London hospitals reducing error of incorrect posts by 70%.
- Developed and maintained an up-to-date database of contacts, ensuring accurate and timely communication.

## Full-Stack Developer

 $\mathrm{Mar}\ 2023$  - Nov2023

Freelance

London, UK

- Developing, optimising and maintaining the websites and applications utilising HTML, CSS, SQL. JavaScript, React and various APIs to meet my clients needs and goals.
- Coding design mock ups into pixel perfect, cross browser compatible, search engine friendly websites.
- Responsible from concept to completion while managing outside vendors, diagnosing, troubleshooting and resolving the issues with website, server and/or third-party integration.

## Full-Stack Developer

Mar 2022 - Jun 2022

3W Creators LLP

London (Remote)

- Developed a content management system for a media company that reduced maintenance costs by 20%
- Completed 3 full web front ends using HTML, CSS, JS, Node, Express, React and SQL.
- Responsible from concept to completion while managing outside vendors, diagnosing, troubleshooting and resolving the issues with website, server and/or third-party integration.

**Head of Sales** 

May 2018 - Mar 2022

Gujarat University

Ahmedabad, India

- To assist and counsel the students regarding their post graduation academics and future learning routes such as Cyber Security.
- $\bullet$  To connect, arrange interviews and manage placements for the students and conducted over 50 workshops with 85% employment turnover rate.
- Researched and presented upcoming technologies to board members for inclusion in courses that increased course enlisting by 60%.

### **PROJECTS**

**Recipe Diary** This is a RESTful web-app providing recipe management for users. With CRUD endpoints to recipes, along with user authentication and personalised dashboard, managing your favourite recipes in one place has made it more convenient. (Repo Link)

SayIt A content management system created to act as a forum for anonymous users to express their thoughts. The functionality had likes, react via emoticons and comment features such that users can interact with posts. (Repo Link)

Voyage A website created from my hobby of travelling. This is my current running project encompassing user registration, wish-list destinations on dashboard and search ability for locations with a response of key facts and things-to-do. (Repo Link)

### **EDUCATION**

### Software Developer Bootcamp, La Fosse Academy

July 2022 - September 2022

A 3-month intensive taught course covering HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React and Python with databases such as MongoDB and PostgreSQL alongside 7 hands-on industry projects with Agile Methodology using Trello

Bachelor of Science in Hospitality Management, MS University, Vadodara, India

2011 - 2014